ajagz.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy | AJAGZ

Note: We do not disclose any of your personal information. In fact we delete everything you gave in our site about you (to play the games and quizzes) after 60 days at max from when you created your link.

### Our Privacy Policy

The privacy and security of our users is at most important to us. This privacy policy document outlines how user information is handled by us and how they are used.

#### Cookies

We use cookies to store user preferences and related information for the web pages that the users access or visit. These information are neither misused nor disclosed to any third party websites and are strictly used only to customize our web page content, identify your browser and serve you based on your previous or current activity, collect site traffic and related information to offer better site experience in future.

If you turn off cookies, some of your activities are unnoticed by us, which reduces the speed or performance of our service. However you can still use our site with better quality of service as the site is effectively optimized for good user experience.

#### Third Party Disclosure

We assure you that we do not disclose, sell, trade or transfer your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) to any outside websites, apps or vendors for any business, commercial or other purposes without your permission. However this is not applicable to our website hosting partners and other service providers who assist us operating our website, servicing you or running our business, so as long as they agree to keep the information confidential.

#### Third Party links

Occasionally, during site creation or optimization, we may include third party services, links or advertisements on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies and therefore we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites and vendors.

#### Google Adsense

This is a third party ad service provider and it may appear on our web pages, which comes directly to your browsers. Google Adsense may receive your IP address when this occurs and our website has no access or control over this third party ad provider. You should consult the respective privacy policies of Google Adsense for more detailed information on their activities.

For your queries and clarifications about our privacy policy, terms of use or site information, feel free to contact us. We welcome any feedback about our site activity and experience.
